ACWA Master Tapes of Interviews with Retirees 5674 OHM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACWA Master Tapes of Interviews with Retirees
1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Miller, Eugene
Colavincenzo, Hector
DeFelice, Orestes
Falk, Rose
Valliani, Maria
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA)
5674 OHM
1.11 cubic feet
1.1 linear feet.
Transcripts, audiovisual materials, interviews.
Audio tape interviews with ACWA retirees
5689666
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 17, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 OH: ACWA Oral History Project Records 5674 OHT: ACWA Transcripts of Interviews with Retirees
Clothing workers--United States.; Clothing workers-- Retirement --United States.; Miller, Eugene; Colavincenzo, Hector; DeFelice, Orestes; Falk, Rose; Valliani, Maria; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
5689666
- Henrico Giudetti, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  ACWA Retiree, Secretary, Local 270 (Italian) 1923-1957 --- 3/23/1981 by E. Miller
- Clementi DeRosa and Wife, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  ACWA Retiree -- 1910-1968) -- Interviewed by Gene Miller 3/2/1981
- John "Patsy" DeRosa and Wife, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  ACWA Retiree, Organizer - Chicago --- 3/12/1981 interviewed by Gene Miller
- Marino Mazzei, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Worker-Owner of Italian Publishing Co. (Chicago) -- 1920's-1930's; Printing House of the Federazione Socialista Italiana of America ---- 4/1/1981 by E. Miller
- Rose Falk, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  ACWA Retiree - Last President of Women's Local 275 --- Interviewed by Gene Miller --- 3/24/1981
- Orestes De Felice, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  ACWA Retiree -- First President (1920) - Local 270 (Italian) --- 3/13/1981 & 4/5/1981 by E. Miller
- Maria Valliani, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  ACWA Retiree --- 3/27/1981 by E. Miller
- Antonio Paone, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  President Local 270, ACWA, 1940-1961, Retired -- Interviewed 9/17/1981 by E. Miller
- Rose Falk (Priola), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  ACWA Retiree - Former President Local 275 (All Womens) -- 3/24/1981 by E. Miller
- Hector Cola Vincenzo, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  ACWA Retiree - Interviewed by Gene Miller at ACWA Center, Chicago -- 1/23/1981